L’Aerophile Collection
Science, Technology, & Business Division, Library of Congress
- Aviators and Designers (Box 130-150A)
  - Group photos. (Box 149)
    - Group Photos (France) #7B. (Envelope 9)
    - Group Photos (France) #8. (Envelope 10)
    - Group Photos (France) #9. (Envelope 11)
    - Group Photos (France) #10. (Envelope 12)
  - Group Photos 11-17. (Box 150)
    - Group Photos (France) #11. (Envelope 1)
    - Group Photos (France) #12. (Envelope 2)
    - Group Photos (France) #13. (Envelope 3)
    - Group Photos (France) #14. (Envelope 4)
    - Group Photos (France) #15. (Envelope 5)
    - Group Photos (France) #16. (Envelope 6)
    - Group Photos (France) #17. (Envelope 7)
  - Groups Photos 18-21. (Box 150A)
    - Group Photos (France) #18. (Envelope 1)
    - Group Photos (France) #19. (Envelope 2)
    - Group Photos (France) #20. (Envelope 3)
    - Group Photos (France) #21. (Envelope 4)
Bibliography
L'Aerophile. Paris: Blondel la Rougery, Vol. 1 - Vol. 54 (1893-1947). LC CALL NUMBER: TL502 A16
The Aeronautical journal. London: Aeronautical Society of Great Britain, Vol. 1 - Vol. 26 (1897-1922).
LC CALL NUMBER: TL501 .R7
Chambe, Rene. Histoire De L'Aviation. France: Flammarion, 1958. 521 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL515 .C37 1958
Chant, Christopher. Aviation: An Illustrated History. London: Orbis Publishing Limited, 1983. 352 p.
CALL NUMBER: TL515 .C383 1983b
Deutsche Zeitschrift für Luftschiffahrt. Berlin: Vereingte Verlagsanstalten Gustav Braunbeck & Gutenberg-Druckerei Aktiengesellschaft, 1908 - 1919.
LC CALL NUMBER: Microfilm 27692
Flight: A Journal Devoted to the Interests, Practice, and Progress of Aerial Locomotion and Transport. London: St. Martin's Lane, Vol 1 - Vol. 9 (1909-1917).
LC CALL NUMBER: TL501 .F5
Jackson, Robert. Fighter pilots of World War I. New York: St. Martin's Press, 1977. 152 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: D600 .J33 1977
Lindbergh, Charles A. " We": the famous flier's own story of his life and his transatlantic flight, together with his views on the future of aviation. New York: G.P. Putnam's Sons, 1927. 308 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL540.L5 A3 1927c
Lomax, Judy. Women of the air. New York, N.Y.: Dodd, Mead, 1987. 216 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL539 .L55 1987
Mouillard, Louis Pierre. L'Empire De L'Air: Essai D'Ornithologie Appliquèe A L'Aviation. Paris: G. Masson, 1881.
284 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL575 .M6 (Rare Book Collection)
Matthews, Hart. Pioneer aviators of the world: a biographical dictionary of the first pilots of 100 countries. Jefferson, N.C.: McFarland & Co., 2003. 208 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL539 .M3235 2003
Rolt, L.T.C. The Aeronauts: A History of Ballooning - 1783-1903. New York: Walker and Company, 1966. 267 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL616 .R63 1966
Smith-Gibbs, C. H. A History of Flying. New York: Walker and Company, 1966. 267 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL616 .R63 1966
Villard, Henry Serrano. Contact!: the story of the early aviators. Mineola, N.Y.: Dover Publications, 2002. 277 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL670.3 .V55 2002
Wohl, Robert. A Passion For Wings: aviation and the Western imagination, 1908-1918. New Haven and London: Yale University Press, 1994. 320 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL526.E85 W65 1994
Wragg, David W. Flight before Flying. New York: Frederick Fell Publishers, Inc., 1974. 191 p.
LC CALL NUMBER: TL515 .W7 1974